<!-- Plugin Configuration File. Read more: https://plugins.jetbrains.com/docs/intellij/plugin-configuration-file.html -->
<idea-plugin>
    <id>com.huayi.intellijplatform.gitstats</id>
    <name>GitStats</name>
    <vendor>huayi</vendor>
    <description><![CDATA[
        <p><strong>Git activity statistics for JetBrains IDEs.</strong></p>
        <p>GitStats turns the Git history of your current project into a clear author-level activity report inside the IDE. Review contribution trends, compare code changes across teammates, and share the visible results without leaving your development workflow.</p>
        <ul>
            <li><strong>Author-level summaries:</strong> compare commits, added lines, deleted lines, and modified files.</li>
            <li><strong>Flexible date ranges:</strong> inspect this week, the last 7 days, this month, or a custom range.</li>
            <li><strong>Author filtering:</strong> narrow large repositories down to the contributors you want to review.</li>
            <li><strong>Two calculation modes:</strong> use Fast Summary for quick line-based ranking, or Detailed mode when commit counts matter.</li>
            <li><strong>Noise control:</strong> exclude generated folders, vendor code, build outputs, or any project-relative paths.</li>
            <li><strong>Shareable results:</strong> copy selected rows, copy the full table, or export the visible statistics as CSV.</li>
        </ul>
        <h3>Getting Started</h3>
        <ol>
            <li>Open a project backed by a Git repository in any supported JetBrains IDE.</li>
            <li>Open the <strong>Git Stats</strong> tool window.</li>
            <li>Choose a date range and optionally filter by author.</li>
            <li>Click <strong>Refresh</strong> to calculate the report.</li>
            <li>Use the settings action to switch modes or exclude noisy paths such as generated files and build outputs.</li>
        </ol>
        <p><strong>Privacy-friendly by design:</strong> GitStats uses the Git executable configured in your IDE and reads only local repository history. No source code, commit data, or statistics are sent to external services.</p>
    ]]></description>

    <depends>com.intellij.modules.platform</depends>
    <depends>com.intellij.modules.vcs</depends>
    <depends>Git4Idea</depends>
<!--    <depends optional="true" config-file="plugin-with-Git4Idea.xml">Git4Idea</depends>-->

    <resource-bundle>messages.MyBundle</resource-bundle>

    <extensions defaultExtensionNs="com.intellij">
        <toolWindow id="Git Stats" secondary="true" icon="/META-INF/icon.svg" anchor="bottom"
                    factoryClass="com.huayi.intellijplatform.gitstats.toolWindow.GitStatsWindowFactory"/>
        <notificationGroup id="GitStats" displayType="BALLOON"/>
    </extensions>

</idea-plugin>
